<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Woof</string>
    <string name="beagle">Beagle</string>
    <string name="beagle_species">Small and Large</string>
    <string name="beagle_description">Beagles are a compact, friendly scent hound breed, known for their short, tricolored coats, floppy ears, and keen sense of smell.</string>
    <string name="belgian_shepherd">Belgian Shepherds</string>
    <string name="belgian_shepherd_species">The Groenendael, The Tervueren, The Laekenois and The Malinois</string>
    <string name="belgian_shepherd_description">Belgian Shepherds are a versatile, intelligent, and energetic herding breed known for their loyalty and protective nature.</string>
    <string name="boxer">Boxer</string>
    <string name="boxer_species">German, American and UK boxers.</string>
    <string name="boxer_description">Boxers are a medium to large, short-haired dog breed known for their muscular build, square-shaped head, and smooth coat.</string>
    <string name="bulldog">Bulldog</string>
    <string name="bulldog_species">American, French, English, Olde English Bulldogge, Dogue de Bordeaux, etc.</string>
    <string name="bulldog_description">Bulldogs are characterized by their short, muscular build, wrinkled face, and distinctive, slightly upturned snout.</string>
    <string name="collie">Collie</string>
    <string name="collie_species">Rough, Smooth, Bearded, Border</string>
    <string name="collie_description">Collie is a medium to large breed of dog, recognized for its long, elegant coat, intelligence and loyalty.</string>
    <string name="corgi">Corgi</string>
    <string name="corgi_species">The Cardigan Welsh and Pembroke Welsh Corgi</string>
    <string name="corgi_description">Corgis are small to medium-sized, low-set herding dogs with short legs and a long, stocky body, known for their affectionate and loyal personalities</string>
    <string name="doberman">Doberman</string>
    <string name="doberman_species">German Pinscher, Old German Shepherd, Rottweiler</string>
    <string name="doberman_description">Doberman Pinschers are a sleek, powerful breed known for their intelligence, loyalty, and protective nature.</string>
    <string name="german_shepherd">German Shepherd</string>
    <string name="german_shepherd_species">East German, West German, American/Canadian</string>
    <string name="german_shepherd_description">German Shepherds are renowned for their intelligence, loyalty, and trainability, making them a popular choice for various roles, including working dogs, guide dogs, and family pets</string>
    <string name="golden_retriever">Golden retriever</string>
    <string name="golden_retriever_species">American, English and Canadian</string>
    <string name="golden_retriever_description">Golden Retrievers are known for their golden-brown coat, gentle nature, and intelligence. </string>
    <string name="husky">Husky</string>
    <string name="husky_species">Siberian, Alaskan. Mackenzie River, Greenland, East Siberian</string>
    <string name="husky_description">Siberian Huskies are medium-sized, athletic dogs known for their endurance and thick, double coat. </string>
    <string name="labrador">Labrador</string>
    <string name="labrador_species">American and English</string>
    <string name="labrador_description">Labrador Retrievers are known for their sturdy, muscular build, short, dense, water-repellent coat, and "otter-like" tail</string>
    <string name="poodle">Poodle</string>
    <string name="poodle_species">Standard, Toy, Labradoodle, Miniature, Cockapoo</string>
    <string name="poodle_description">Poodles are known for their intelligence, athleticism, and distinctive curly coat.</string>
    <string name="rottweiler">Rottweiler</string>
    <string name="rottweiler_species">American, German or Roman</string>
    <string name="rottweiler_description">The Rottweiler is a muscular, robust and very strong dog, known for its black coat with rust markings.</string>
    <string name="shiba">Shiba Inu</string>
    <string name="shiba_species">Shinshu, Sanin, Mino</string>
    <string name="shiba_description">The Shiba Inu is a medium-sized, agile dog breed originating in Japan. It was originally bred and developed as a hunting dog, and is therefore capable of handling mountainous terrain.</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more information</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
</resources>